agaricdesign.com 2019-11-14

# Privacy policy

Respecting your privacy and being responsible with the data we collect from you is of the utmost importance to us.  We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this privacy policy.

## Information collection and use

If you choose to leave a comment or a private message through our contact form, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including your name and email address. The information that we collect will be used to contact or identify you.

## Log data

We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.

## Cookies

We do not use cookies for visitors to our site. (Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used as an anonymous unique identifier.)

## Service providers

We employ a third-party company, Google, to assist us in analyzing how our website is used. Only anonymized data is collected.

Hotjar assists its us in providing our end users with a better experience and service as well as assist us in diagnosing technical problems and analyzing user trends. Most importantly, through Hotjar’s services, the functionality of the site can be improved, making them more user-friendly, more valuable, and simpler to use for the end users.

You may opt-out from having Hotjar collect your information when visiting a Hotjar Enabled Site at any time by visiting our [Opt-out page](https://www.hotjar.com/opt-out) and clicking ‘Disable Hotjar’ or enabling Do Not Track (DNT) in your browser.

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

## Contact us

If you have any questions or suggestions about our privacy policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
